Hrishikesh Rai



hkrai39@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/hrishikesh-rai



https://hrishikeshrai.netlify.app/

Summary

I'm a proficient developer with industry experience building website and web applications. I specialize in JavaScript and have professional experience working with React.js and Next.js. I also have experience working with Node, VueJS, Gatsby, Typescript and MongoDB. Take a look at my work or get in touch! hrishikeshrai.netlify.app/

Experience



Glance

Jan 2022 - Present (1 year 5 months)



SDE - 1

Park+

Dec 2020 - Dec 2021 (1 year 1 month)

Did SEO optimisation for some of our product, built around 200+ pages resulting from 7K impression per month to 28K in first 28 days (480K impression currently(2022).

Optimized performance of our website, improved score from 18 to 55 avg. (hitting 70+ in some of our pages) which improved our search engine rankings.

Built our customer support page to resolve query of our customers resulting in +50% more customer satisfaction in quick & maintainable fashion.

Built landing page of Park+, and many other products like Car Wash, Car check-up, Discover (our customer engagement platform), Challan, Sell Car in integration with Spinny & Car Dekho.

Built FASTag product along with my colleague in just 1 and half day, which resulted generating 1cr revenue within first month.

Education



Rajiv Gandhi Prodyogiki Vishwavidyalaya

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Computer Science 2016 - 2020

Skills

JavaScript • React.js • Front-end Development • Object-Oriented Programming (OOP) • Node.js • Vue.js • REST APIs • HTML5 • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • MongoDB